<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ACM REP 2025</title><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/</link><atom:link href="https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>ACM REP 2025</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><image><url>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/media/logo_hu61cdae111572e3e5936dfba729510bed_59569_300x300_fit_lanczos_3.png</url><title>ACM REP 2025</title><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/</link></image><item><title>Sponsors</title><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/sponsor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/sponsor/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Travel &amp; Venue</title><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/venue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/venue/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Featured Keynote Speakers</title><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/keynotes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/keynotes/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/admin/config.yml</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/admin/config.yml</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/cfp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/cfp/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/cft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/cft/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/conduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/conduct/</guid><description>&lt;div class="alert alert-warning">
&lt;div>
Under construction &amp;ndash; Will be completed soon.
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;p>The steering committee of ACM REP &amp;lsquo;24 believes in respect, compassion, understanding and inclusion and we expect all community members to act in accordance with these values. Fostering the free exchange of ideas requires building a conference that welcomes people of all backgrounds. Diversity of opinion and background is a fundamental strength of our community. The members of our community must have the freedom to espouse and explore a wide range of ideas. Toward that goal, ACM REP &amp;lsquo;24 aims to create spaces where every participant can express themselves without fear of judgment or harassment.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The ACM REP Code of Conduct guides the expected, professional behavior of conference participants, including:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Treating everyone with respect and consideration; under the umbrella of respect, we expect all participants to be mindful of their speech and behaviors both in person and online.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Communicating openly and thoughtfully with others and being considerate of the multitude of views and opinions that may be different than your own.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Being respectful and mindful in your critique of ideas.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Being mindful of your fellow participants, including (but not limited to):
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Respecting participants wishes to not be photographed;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Respecting participant gender pronouns; and&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Respecting the space of others and their right to engage or not engage in conversation.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>We believe differences of opinion are a natural part of social and academic life and are important to work through when building community and learning from one another. At the same time, we acknowledge that societal power structures are even more challenging in academia, which is an inherently hierarchical community. In order to foster an environment of inclusion, we do not tolerate harassment, discrimination, or abuse in any form. Participants who engage in harassment may be removed from the conference at the discretion of the organizers.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="unacceptable-behaviors-include-but-are-not-limited-to">Unacceptable behaviors include, but are not limited to:&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>intimidating, harassing, abusive, discriminatory, derogatory or demeaning speech or actions by any participant in ACM-REP activities, at all related events and in one-on-one communications carried out in the context of conference activities;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>offensive, degrading, humiliating, harmful, or prejudicial verbal or written comments or visual images related to gender, sexual orientation, race, religion, disability, age, appearance, or other personal characteristics;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>unwelcome sexual advances, requests for sexual favors, or other verbal/physical conduct of a sexual nature;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>inappropriate or gratuitous use of nudity, sexual images, or stereotyped images including using an activity-related communication channel to display or distribute sexually explicit or otherwise offensive or discriminatory images or messages;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>deliberate intimidation, stalking or following;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>harassing photography or recording;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>sustained disruption of talks or other events;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>unwelcome and uninvited attention or contact;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>physical assault (including unwelcome touch or groping);&lt;/li>
&lt;li>real or implied threat of physical harm;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>real or implied threat of professional or financial damage or harm.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Harassment can occur when there is no deliberate intention to offend. Be careful in the words that you choose. Harassment committed in a joking manner or disguised as a compliment still constitutes unacceptable behavior. Remember that sexist, racist, and other exclusionary jokes can be offensive to those around you.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="consequences-of-unacceptable-behavior">Consequences of Unacceptable Behavior&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If an ACM-REP participant engages in prohibited behavior, the conference committee reserves the right to take any action the committee deems appropriate, including removing the participant from the conference.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="how-to-report-unacceptable-behavior">How to Report Unacceptable Behavior&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In the event of unacceptable behavior, participants may wish to inform a person in authority. During ACM REP, participants should reach out to one of the General or Program Chairs (see list below). These individuals can provide information about the process for handling complaints or handling immediate onsite needs.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="alert alert-note">
&lt;div>
There may be cases (such as those involving Title IX issues in the United States and venue- or employer-specific policies) where an on-site person who is informed of harassment will be required to file a complaint.
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;p>General Chairs: Tanu Malik &amp;amp; Jay Lofstead&lt;br>
Program Chairs: TBD&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This code of content was adapted from the &lt;a href="https://www.acm.org/about-acm/policy-against-harassment" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Policy Against Harassment at ACM Activities&lt;/a> and the &lt;a href="https://cscw.acm.org/2019/code-of-conduct.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ACM CSCW 2019 conference code of conduct&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Diversity &amp; Inclusion</title><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/diversity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/diversity/</guid><description>&lt;div class="alert alert-warning">
&lt;div>
Under construction &amp;ndash; Will be completed soon.
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>ACM REP is committed to Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion in Computing and Reproducibility.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Following &lt;a href="https://www.acm.org/diversity-inclusion/about" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the model set forth by the overall ACM community&lt;/a>, the ACM REP community encompasses the wide range and diverse set of professionals working on reproducibility and computing, from educators and researchers to software and hardware developers, system engineers, project managers, and data scientists.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As noted by the ACM, &amp;ldquo;Diversity is achieved when the individuals around the table are drawn from a variety of backgrounds and experience, leading to a breadth of viewpoints, reasoning, and approaches [&amp;hellip;] Equity is achieved by supporting the participation of marginalized communities in computing as well as by promoting impartiality and fairness within the procedures, processes, and distribution of resources and systems [&amp;hellip;] [and] Inclusion is achieved when the environment is characterized by behaviors that welcome and embrace diversity.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ACM REP is committed to creating an environment that welcomes new ideas and perspectives, and where hostility or other antisocial behaviors are not tolerated. Conference organizers welcome participation and contribution from participants representing different ages, races, genders and sexual orientation, nationality, physical ability, thinking style and experiences to enhance the overall richness in providing quality programs and services for the global community. We also recognize the need to make services, activities, events, etc. more inclusive for individuals with disabilities. We are open to make accommodations and arrangements so that all those interested can participate fully in our events and activities.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Health &amp; Safety</title><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/health/</guid><description>&lt;div class="alert alert-warning">
&lt;div>
Under construction &amp;ndash; Will be completed soon.
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;p>We are delighted to welcome attendees to our meeting at INRIA, Rennes University, while also acknowledging continued concerns about the spread of COVID and other health and safety issues. Our team is monitoring the latest guidance and regulations, and our policies align with public health orders. We will follow venue and local regulations regarding masking, distancing, and related health measures.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Proof of COVID-19 vaccinations or a recent negative COVID-19 test result is currently not required for this event. However, If you are feeling sick or test positive for COVID, do not attend the meeting. We are relying on the responsible behavior of our attendees. We encourage but do not require the wearing of masks by attendees. Masks will be made available at the conference venue. Note that for all hospitality related activities, attendees will have the option to eat meals or partake in coffee breaks outdoors if they desire.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If there are any changes in vaccination and/or masking requirements, participants will be emailed prior to the meeting and new requirements will be posted on this page.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We kindly ask that attendees please consult and follow TBD guidelines for quarantine and isolation and travel (as they may change) prior to traveling for the meeting.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>During the meeting, participants are encouraged to:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Monitor for symptoms of COVID each morning before coming to the meeting.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Consider bringing a rapid COVID test kit in case you experience symptoms.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Wear a high-quality mask&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>If you experience symptoms of COVID and/or test positive for COVID while attending ACM REP, you are strongly requested to:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Notify colleagues that they may have been exposed.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Adjust your accommodations and travel plans to follow TBD guidelines for quarantining.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Refrain from attending any meeting events.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Housing</title><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/housing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/housing/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="hotels">Hotels&lt;/h1>
&lt;div class="alert alert-warning">
&lt;div>
Under construction &amp;ndash; Will be completed soon.
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Registration</title><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/registration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/registration/</guid><description>&lt;div class="alert alert-warning">
&lt;div>
Under construction &amp;ndash; Will be completed soon.
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acm-rep.github.io/2025/schedule/</guid><description>&lt;div class="alert alert-warning">
&lt;div>
Under construction &amp;ndash; Will be completed soon.
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div></description></item></channel></rss>